{"ResponseId": {"question": "ID", "answers": "code respondent", "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "general"}, "Q4": {"question": "In general, in the month before the lockdown, would you say your health was:", "answers": {"0": "Poor", "1": "Fair", "2": "Good", "3": "Very good", "4": "Excellent"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_1": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in vigorous activities, such as running, lifting heavy objects, participating in strenuous sports?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_2": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in moderate activities, such as moving a table, pushing a vacuum cleaner, bowling, or playing golf?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_3": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in lifting or carrying groceries?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_4": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in climbing several flights of stairs?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_5": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in climbing one flight of stairs?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_6": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in bending, kneeling, or stooping?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_7": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in walking more than a mile?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_8": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in walking several blocks?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_9": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in walking one block?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q6_10": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did your health limit you in bathing or dressing yourself?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q9_1": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, had you cut down the amount of time you spent on work or other daily activities as a result of your physical health?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q9_2": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, had you accomplished less than you would like on work or other daily activities as a result of your physical health?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q9_3": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, had you been limited in the kind of work or other daily activities as a result of your physical health?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q9_4": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, had you had difficulty performing the work or other daily activities (for example, it took extra effort) as a result of your physical health?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q10_1": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, had you cut down the amount of time you spent on work or other daily activities as a result of any emotional problems (such as feeling depressed or anxious)?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q10_2": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, had you accomplished less than you would like on work or other daily activities as a result of any emotional problems (such as feeling depressed or anxious)?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q10_3": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, had you not do work or other daily activity as carfully as usual as a result of any emotional problems (such as feeling depressed or anxious)?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q11": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did emotional problems interfered with your normal social activities with family, friends, neighbors, or groups?", "answers": {"0": "Not at all", "1": "Slightly", "2": "Moderately", "3": "Severe", "4": "Very severe"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q12": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, how much bodily pain have you had?", "answers": {"0": "None", "1": "Very mild", "2": "Mild", "3": "Moderate", "4": "Severe", "5": "Very severe"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q13": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, how much did pain interfere with your normal work (including both work outside the home and housework)?", "answers": {"0": "Not at all", "1": "A little bit", "2": "Moderately", "3": "Quite a bit", "4": "Extremely"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_1": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did you feel full of pep?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_2": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, have you been a very nervous person?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_3": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, have you felt so down in the dumps that nothing could cheer you up?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_4": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, have you felt calm and peaceful?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_5": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did you have a lot of energy?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_6": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, have you felt downhearted and blue?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_7": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did you feel worn out?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_8": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, have you been a happy person?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q14_9": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, did you feel tired?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q15": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, how much of the time has your physical health or emotional problems interfered with your social activities (like visiting with friends, relatives, etc.)?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q16_1": {"question": "Referring to the month before the lockdown, how true or false was this statements for you? I seem to get sick a little easier than other people", "answers": {"0": "Definitely false", "1": "Mostly false", "2": "Mostly true", "3": "Definitely true", "4": "Don't know"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q16_2": {"question": "Referring to the month before the lockdown, how true or false was this statements for you? I am as healthy as anybody I know", "answers": {"0": "Definitely false", "1": "Mostly false", "2": "Mostly true", "3": "Definitely true", "4": "Don't know"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q16_3": {"question": "Referring to the month before the lockdown, how true or false was this statements for you? I expect my health to get worse", "answers": {"0": "Definitely false", "1": "Mostly false", "2": "Mostly true", "3": "Definitely true", "4": "Don't know"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q16_4": {"question": "Referring to the month before the lockdown, how true or false was this statements for you? My health is excellent", "answers": {"0": "Definitely false", "1": "Mostly false", "2": "Mostly true", "3": "Definitely true", "4": "Don't know"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q32_1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, on how many days did you do vigorous physical activities like heavy lifting, digging, aerobics, or fast bicycling?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q33": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, how much time did you usually spend doing vigorous physical activities on one of those days?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q35_1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, on how many days did you do moderate physical activities like heavy lifting, digging, aerobics, or fast bicycling?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q36": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, how much time did you usually spend doing moderate physical activities on one of those days?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q38_1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, on how many days did you walk for at least 10 minutes at a time?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q39": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, how much time did you usually spend walking on one of those days?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q40": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, at what pace did you mostly walk?", "answers": {"0": "SLOW pace, with no change in your breathing rate", "1": "MODERATE pace, which made your breathe at a rate that was only moderately faster than normal", "2": "INTENSE pace, which made your breathe at a much faster rate than normal"}, "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q42": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, how much time did you spend sitting on a week day?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q43": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, how much time did you spend sitting on a weekend day?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q59_1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week before the lockdown, how would you rate the overall quality of your sleep?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "SQS", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q74": {"question": "In the month before the lockdown, were you suffering from some pathology, independent of Covid, which may have limited you in your daily activities? (for example, cardio-respiratory diseases, tumors, traumatic events, etc.)", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q17": {"question": "In general, would you say your health is:", "answers": {"0": "Poor", "1": "Fair", "2": "Good", "3": "Very good", "4": "Excellent"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q18": {"question": "Compared to the month before the lockdown, how would you rate your health in general now?", "answers": {"0": "Much worse now than a year ago", "1": "A little worse now than a year ago", "2": "More or less the same as a year ago", "3": "A little better now than a year ago", "4": "Much better now than a year ago"}, "type": "comparison", "period": "comparison"}, "Q19_1": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in vigorous activities, such as running, lifting heavy objects, participating in strenuous sports?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_2": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in moderate activities, such as moving a table, pushing a vacuum cleaner, bowling, or playing golf?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_3": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in lifting or carrying groceries?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_4": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in climbing several flights of stairs?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_5": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in climbing one flight of stairs?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_6": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in bending, kneeling, or stooping?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_7": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in walking more than a mile?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_8": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in walking several blocks?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_9": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in walking one block?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q19_10": {"question": "In the past month, have your health limit you in bathing or dressing yourself?", "answers": {"0": "Yes, Limited a lot", "1": "Yes, Limited a Little", "2": "No, Not Limited at all"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q20_1": {"question": "In the past month, had you cut down the amount of time you spent on work or other daily activities as a result of your physical health?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q20_2": {"question": "In the past month, had you accomplished less than you would like on work or other daily activities as a result of your physical health?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q20_3": {"question": "In the past month, had you been limited in the kind of work or other daily activities as a result of your physical health?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q20_4": {"question": "In the past month, had you had difficulty performing the work or other daily activities (for example, it took extra effort) as a result of your physical health?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q21_1": {"question": "In the past month, had you cut down the amount of time you spent on work or other daily activities as a result of any emotional problems (such as feeling depressed or anxious)?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q21_2": {"question": "In the past month, had you accomplished less than you would like on work or other daily activities as a result of any emotional problems (such as feeling depressed or anxious)?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q21_3": {"question": "In the past month, had you not do work or other daily activity as carfully as usual as a result of any emotional problems (such as feeling depressed or anxious)?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q22": {"question": "In the past month, have emotional problems interfered with your normal social activities with family, friends, neighbors, or groups?", "answers": {"0": "Not at all", "1": "Slightly", "2": "Moderately", "3": "Severe", "4": "Very severe"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q23": {"question": "In the past month, how much bodily pain have you had?", "answers": {"0": "None", "1": "Very mild", "2": "Mild", "3": "Moderate", "4": "Severe", "5": "Very severe"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q24": {"question": "In the past month, how much did pain interfere with your normal work (including both work outside the home and housework)?", "answers": {"0": "Not at all", "1": "A little bit", "2": "Moderately", "3": "Quite a bit", "4": "Extremely"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_1": {"question": "In the past month, have you feel full of pep?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_2": {"question": "In the past month, have you been a very nervous person?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_3": {"question": "In the past month, have you felt so down in the dumps that nothing could cheer you up?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_4": {"question": "In the past month, have you felt calm and peaceful?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_5": {"question": "In the past month, have you have a lot of energy?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_6": {"question": "In the past month, have you felt downhearted and blue?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_7": {"question": "In the past month, have you feel worn out?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_8": {"question": "In the past month, have you been a happy person?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q25_9": {"question": "In the past month, have you feel tired?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q26": {"question": "In the past month, how much of the time has your physical health or emotional problems interfered with your social activities (like visiting with friends, relatives, etc.)?", "answers": {"0": "None of the Time", "1": "A little bit of the time", "2": "Some of the time", "3": "A good Bit of the Time", "4": "Most of the time", "5": "All of the time"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q27_1": {"question": "Referring to the past month, how true or false was this statements for you? I seem to get sick a little easier than other people", "answers": {"0": "Definitely false", "1": "Mostly false", "2": "Mostly true", "3": "Definitely true", "4": "Don't know"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q27_2": {"question": "Referring to the past month, how true or false was this statements for you? I am as healthy as anybody I know", "answers": {"0": "Definitely false", "1": "Mostly false", "2": "Mostly true", "3": "Definitely true", "4": "Don't know"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q27_3": {"question": "Referring to the past month, how true or false was this statements for you? I expect my health to get worse", "answers": {"0": "Definitely false", "1": "Mostly false", "2": "Mostly true", "3": "Definitely true", "4": "Don't know"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q27_4": {"question": "Referring to the past month, how true or false was this statements for you? My health is excellent", "answers": {"0": "Definitely false", "1": "Mostly false", "2": "Mostly true", "3": "Definitely true", "4": "Don't know"}, "type": "SF-36", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q47_1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, on how many days did you do vigorous physical activities like heavy lifting, digging, aerobics, or fast bicycling?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q48": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, how much time did you usually spend doing vigorous physical activities on one of those days?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q49_1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, on how many days did you do moderate physical activities like heavy lifting, digging, aerobics, or fast bicycling?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q50": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, how much time did you usually spend doing moderate physical activities on one of those days?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q52_1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, on how many days did you walk for at least 10 minutes at a time?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q53": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, how much time did you usually spend walking on one of those days?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q54": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, at what pace did you mostly walk?", "answers": {"0": "SLOW pace, with no change in your breathing rate", "1": "MODERATE pace, which made your breathe at a rate that was only moderately faster than normal", "2": "INTENSE pace, which made your breathe at a much faster rate than normal"}, "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q58.1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, how much time did you spend sitting on a week day?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q56": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, how much time did you spend sitting on a weekend day?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "IPAQ", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q60_1": {"question": "Thinking about a typical week in the last month, how would you rate the overall quality of your sleep?", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "SQS", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q75": {"question": "In the past month, were you suffering from some pathology, independent of Covid, which may have limited you in your daily activities? (for example, cardio-respiratory diseases, tumors, traumatic events, etc.)", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q58.2": {"question": "gender", "answers": {"0": "Male", "1": "Female", "2": "Not defined"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "general"}, "Q60_1.1": {"question": "born year", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "general"}, "Q61": {"question": "weight", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "general"}, "Q62": {"question": "Compared to the period before the lock-down, your weight is:", "answers": {"0": "Much decreased", "1": "Slightly decreased", "2": "Stayed the same", "3": "Slightly increased", "4": "Much increased"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q63": {"question": "height", "answers": "continuous variable", "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "general"}, "Q64_1": {"question": "In which region do you live?", "answers": "categorical variable", "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "general"}, "Q65": {"question": "Did your home during the lockdown period have spaces (external or internal) where you could carry out physical activity?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "during"}, "Q66": {"question": "Do you practice any kind of sporting activity?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q67": {"question": "Which sporting activity do you practice?", "answers": "Multiple answer", "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q68": {"question": "How do you practice sport or physical activity?", "answers": {"0": "I do not practice any activities", "1": "I only practice physical activity", "2": "I play sports occasionally", "3": "I play sport continuously"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q69": {"question": "Has the way you do sports changed compared to before the lockdown?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "comparison", "period": "comparison"}, "Q70": {"question": "Which sporting activity did you practice?", "answers": "Multiple answer", "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q71": {"question": "How did you practice sport or physical activity?", "answers": {"0": "I did not practice any activities", "1": "I only practiced physical activity", "2": "I play sports occasionally", "3": "I play sport continuously"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q72": {"question": "Before the lockdown where did you mainly carried out your physical activity?", "answers": {"0": "I did not do physical activity", "1": "at home", "2": "indoors (fitness centers, playgrounds, swimming pools, etc.)", "3": "outdoors (parks, outdoor playgrounds, etc.)"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "before lockdown"}, "Q73": {"question": "After the lockdown where do you mainly carried out your physical activity?", "answers": {"0": "I do not do physical activity", "1": "at home", "2": "indoors (fitness centers, playgrounds, swimming pools, etc.)", "3": "outdoors (parks, outdoor playgrounds, etc.)"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q74_1": {"question": "What kind of work do you do now?", "answers": {"1": "sedentary", "2": "moderate sedentary", "3": "mixed", "4": "moderate active", "5": "active"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "general"}, "Q75.1": {"question": "Have you encountered any known symptoms related to COVID-19?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes, with mild symptoms (home stay)", "2": "Yes, with moderate symptoms (hospitalization with admission to sub-intensive care)", "3": "Yes, with severe symptoms (hospitalization with admission to intensive care)"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "after lockdown"}, "Q76": {"question": "Has the pandemic changed the way you perceive the importance of practicing sports / physical activity regularly?", "answers": {"0": "No", "1": "Yes"}, "type": "comparison", "period": "comparison"}, "Q77": {"question": "Do you think the lockdown changed your overall health?", "answers": {"0": "Much worse", "1": "Got worse", "2": "Stayed the same", "3": "Improved", "4": "Much improved"}, "type": "comparison", "period": "comparison"}, "zone": {"question": "In which Italian zone do you live?", "answers": {"0": "Nord", "1": "Centre", "2": "Sud"}, "type": "respondent characteristics", "period": "general"}}